{"data":[{"question":"Some antibiotics used in the treatment of human disease are like only in that they are obtained from fungi and bacteria.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Some ","b":"are ","c":"like ","d":"in that ","answer":"3","explain":"- like-> alike","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The biggest single hobby in America, the one that Americans spend most time, energy and money, is gardening.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"biggest single ","b":"that ","c":"spend ","d":"is ","answer":"2","explain":"- That-> in that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Constructed in Chicago in 1883, the Home Insurance Building was the first building in the world that the floors and the exterior masonry walls were supported by a skeleton framework of metal.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Constructed ","b":"that ","c":"exterior ","d":"were supported ","answer":"2","explain":"- That-> of that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Advancements in technology are inextricably linked to the strength and survival of the high-tech industry and its  potential to create new jobs.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"inextricably ","b":"survival ","c":"and its  ","d":"potential ","answer":"3","explain":"- And its-> and their","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The chimpanzee possesses hand tool, the sticky termite stick, with which it digs termites out of logs and stumps.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"hand tool","b":"with which ","c":"it ","d":"out of ","answer":"1","explain":"- Hand tool-> handy tool","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"For the past few years, researchers have perfected their control over the movement of cells and microbes by using low-power laser beams.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"few years","b":"have perfected ","c":"their ","d":"using ","answer":"2","explain":"- Have perfected-> have been perfecting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Perhaps the most unique thing about carbon atoms are their ability to combine with themselves.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the most ","b":"about ","c":"are ","d":"to  combine ","answer":"3","explain":"- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Psychologists and psychiatrists are trained to encourage their parents to talk for the things that are causing them difficulty.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are trained ","b":"their ","c":"talk for ","d":"difficulty","answer":"3","explain":"- Talk for-> talk about","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"In mathematical terms, modern algebra is set of objects with rules for connecting or relating those objects.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"terms","b":"is set ","c":"rules ","d":"relating ","answer":"2","explain":"- Is set-> is composed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Pennsylvania has the most institutions of higher learning than any other state has.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the most ","b":"institutions ","c":"any other ","d":"has","answer":"1","explain":"- The most-> more","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"}]}